wowway.com 2017-05-30

# WOW! customer privacy notice

                                 WOW! customer privacy notice
                   for cable television, internet and phone services
As a subscriber to cable service or other services provided by WOW!, you are entitled under Section 631 of the Federal Cable Communications Policy
Act of 1984, as amended, (the “Cable Act”) to information regarding the collection, maintenance and disclosure of personally identifiable information
by cable television operators. We provide this Notice to inform you of: (1) the nature of personally identifiable information we collect and the limitations
imposed by the Cable Act upon cable operators in the collection and disclosure of personally identifiable information about subscribers; (2) the nature
of our use of personally identifiable information; (3) the nature, frequency and purpose of any disclosure which we may make of such information,
including the types of persons to whom we may disclose the information; (4) the period during which we maintain personally identifiable information;
(5) the times and place at which you may have access to your personally identifiable information; and (6) your rights under the Cable Act concerning
personally identifiable information and its collection and disclosure.
Personally identifiable information is information that identifies a particular person; it does not include aggregate data that does not identify a
particular person or persons.
In addition, Section 702 of the federal Telecommunications Act of 1996, as amended, (the “Telecommunications Act”) provides additional privacy
protections for the following information related to phone services: (i) information about the quantity, technical configuration, type, destination,
location, and amount of your use of the phone services; and (ii) information contained on your telephone bill concerning the phone services
you receive. That phone information, when matched to your name, address, and telephone number, is known as customer proprietary network
information or CPNI for short. This notice, which includes our CPNI Policy, describes what CPNI information we obtain, how we protect it, and how
it may be used.
Pursuant to an order of the Federal Communications Commission (the FCC), the broadband Internet access service offered by WOW! on a retail,
mass-market basis is now classified as a “telecommunications service.” Certain information relating to your use of our broadband Internet access
service will be considered CPNI and subject to additional privacy protections and use restrictions contained in federal law, but not to the FCC’s
related rules implementing that law, many of which were designed specifically for telephone service. In the absence of specific guidance from the
FCC, we will take reasonable, good faith steps to protect the CPNI of our broadband Internet access service customers in accordance with the
requirements of federal law, as applicable, and as described in this privacy notice.
WOW! provides IP-enabled or “VoIP” phone service in all of its operating regions. In some service areas, WOW! also provides both VoIP and traditional
circuit switched phone service (“Traditional Phone”). In an Order released by the Federal Communications Commission in April 2007, the Commission
modified its rules regarding CPNI, and also determined that its rules (as modified) regarding CPNI apply to VoIP services effective December 8, 2007.
If you are a customer of our Traditional Phone services or (effective December 8, 2007) our VoIP phone services, you have the right, and WOW! has
a duty, under the Telecommunications Act, to protect the confidentiality of CPNI. We will also honor any restrictions applied by state law, to the
extent applicable. WE EXPLAIN BELOW IN GREATER DETAIL THE RULES REGARDING CPNI, AND THE CHANGES TO THE RULES THAT BECAME
EFFECTIVE DECEMBER 8, 2007. THE LAW ALLOWS US TO USE YOUR CPNI FOR CERTAIN PURPOSES (EXPLAINED BELOW UNDER “GIVING OR
WITHHOLDING YOUR APPROVAL FOR WOW! TO USE CPNI TO MARKET ADDITIONAL PRODUCTS AND SERVICES TO YOU”) UNLESS YOU DENY
OR RESTRICT YOUR APPROVAL. WE WILL ASSUME THAT YOU APPROVE OUR USE OF CPNI FOR THE PURPOSES DESCRIBED BELOW UNLESS
YOU CONTACT US TO DENY OR RESTRICT YOUR APPROVAL.
WE ALSO EXPLAIN BELOW UNDER THE SECTIONS ENTITLED “WOW!’s ‘DO NOT CALL’ AND ‘DO NOT MAIL’ LISTS” AND “EMAIL AND OTHER
COMMUNICATIONS FROM WOW!” HOW WE INTEND TO COMMUNICATE WITH YOU BY EMAIL AND PHONE (WHICH MAY INCLUDE AUTODIALED
CALLS AND PRE-RECORDED OR ARTIFICIAL VOICE MESSAGES TO A CELL OR OTHER PHONE NUMBER THAT YOU PROVIDE TO US) AND YOUR
ABILITY TO LIMIT OR RESTRICT CERTAIN COMMUNICATIONS.
In this notice, the terms “WOW!,” “we,” “us,” or “our” refer to the operating company affiliate of WOW! Internet, Cable and Phone that owns and/
or operates the cable television system in your area pursuant to a cable television franchise or other authority with the local or state franchising
authority. The term “you” refers to you as a subscriber to our cable service or other services.
I. COLLECTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION AND CPNI
The Cable Act applies to personally identifiable information (PII) that you have furnished to WOW!, or that WOW! has collected using the cable
system, in connection with the provision of cable service or other services. As further described below in “The kind of personally identifiable
information and CPNI that WOW! collects,” PII is information that identifies or can be used to identify you such as: your name, address, phone
number, fax number, email address, birth date, names of household members, driver’s license or state ID number, social security number, bank
account information and credit card information. PII does not include, among other things, any aggregate data or other data which does not identify
you. The Telecommunications Act applies to CPNI related to our regulated phone services, and certain orders of the Federal Communications
Commission apply the CPNI rules to our VoIP services. This notice applies to our cable television service, our high-speed Internet service, and our
phone services as provided for by applicable law and except as otherwise noted. This notice only covers information that is collected by WOW! in
connection with the provision of our cable television service, our Internet service, and our phone services to you as a subscriber to one or more of
these services. It does not cover information that may be collected through any other products, services, or websites, even if accessed through our
services and even if co-branded with them. You should read the privacy policies for these other products, services, and websites to learn how they
handle your personal information.

Purposes for which WOW! may collect personally identifiable information and CPNI
The Cable Act authorizes WOW! as a cable operator to use the cable system to collect personally identifiable information concerning any subscriber:
(i) in order to obtain information necessary to render our cable service or other services to our subscribers; and (ii) to detect unauthorized reception
of cable communications. The Cable Act prohibits us from using the cable system to collect personally identifiable information concerning any
subscriber for any purposes other than those listed above without the subscriber’s prior written or electronic consent.
The Telecommunications Act authorizes us to use, disclose, or permit access to individually identifiable CPNI in our provision of (i) the
telecommunications service from which this information is derived; or (ii) services necessary to, or used in, the provision of these services, including
the publishing of directories. The Telecommunications Act prohibits us from using CPNI for any purposes other than those listed above except as
permitted or required by law or with your approval.
The kind of personally identifiable information and CPNI that WOW! collects
WOW! collects information from you at several different points when you initiate and use our services. Some of this information is personally
identifiable information, but much of it is not. For example, PII does not include, among other things, any aggregate data or other data which does
not identify you (for example, information that is collected anonymously, or has been anonymized or aggregated so that it cannot identify you, or
demographic information not connected to an identified individual or household) or information which by itself does not identify you, such as, for
example, your zip code, gender, IP address, MAC address or other equipment identifiers. We do collect certain personally identifiable information
that our subscribers furnish to us in connection with the provision of cable service or other services. In order to provide reliable, high quality service
to you, we keep regular business records containing information about you that may constitute personally identifiable information. These records
include some, but typically not all, of the following information: (i) your name; (ii) service address; (iii) billing address; (iv) email address; (v) telephone
number; (vi) driver’s license number; (vii) social security number; (viii) bank account number; (ix) credit card number; and (x) other similar account
information.
With respect to phone services, examples of CPNI include information typically available from telephone-related details on your monthly bill, such
as: (i) location of service; (ii) technical configuration of service; (iii) type of service; (iv) quantity of service; (v) amount of use of service; (vi) calling
patterns; and (vii) other information contained on your bill for local and long distance services.
CPNI does not include your name, address, and telephone number, because the Telecommunications Act classifies that information as “subscriber
list information” which is not subject to the protections applicable to CPNI. However, that information is also subject to certain protections as
described below under “Disclosure of your personally identifiable information and CPNI.” We also collect and maintain certain other information about
your account. For example, this information may include: (i) billing, payment, and deposit history; (ii) additional service information; (iii) customer
correspondence and communications records; (iv) maintenance and complaint information; (v) records indicating the number of television sets,
set-top boxes, modems, or telephones connected to our cable system; and (vi) additional information about the service options you have chosen.
Some of our services permit you to establish secondary accounts, and if you do so we collect similar information in order to establish and service
the secondary accounts. During the initial provisioning of our services, and during any subsequent changes or updates to our services, WOW! may
collect technical information about your televisions, any set-top boxes, computer hardware and software, cable modems, telephones, and/or other
cable or other service-related devices, and customization settings and preferences. Additionally, if you rent your residence, we may have a record
of whether landlord permission was required prior to installing our cable facilities as well as your landlord’s name and address.
The kind of information we collect with our cable system and equipment
When you use our interactive or other transactional services such as video on demand or Online Content, for example, our systems and equipment
may automatically collect certain information about your use of these services. Most of this information is not personally identifiable information
and it is simply used, for example, to carry out a particular request you make using your remote control, set-top box, DVR, computer, remote access
device or other equipment. This may include information required to change your television channel, review listings in an electronic program guide,
pause or fast forward through certain video on demand programs, or invoke a calling feature for our phone service, among other things. It may also
include other information such as the time you actually use our services and the use of other features of our services, and which menus and menu
screens are used most often and the time spent using them. In order to carry out a particular request you make to watch a pay-per-view program
or purchase a product, service, or feature, for example, our system may collect certain personally identifiable information. This information typically
consists of account and billing-related information such as the pay-per-view programs or other products, services, or features ordered so that you
may be properly billed for them.
In addition, our cable systems may also collect anonymous and/or aggregate information using set-top boxes and other equipment. Anonymous
information does not include (or has been stripped of) information that could be used to identify you. We or our suppliers may collect, use and
store this information to determine things like which programs are being watched and which are most popular (including things like the number of
times a program is watched per date, the average length of time a program is watched and how many people watch a program to its conclusion),
whether people are watching commercials, as well as other audience-measurement focused information, for example. As described further below
under “Use of your personally identifiable information and CPNI,” this type of anonymous information may be used by us for any reason and shared
with affiliates, partners and other third parties, including advertisers, content providers, data companies, ratings agencies, audience measurement
and market research firms. We generally use this information to provide the services that you subscribe to, and for other purposes that may
include but not be limited to improving our cable television service and other services, providing you with more relevant programming, advertising
and features, increasing the value of the services, providing you with information or offers about products or services that we believe may be of
interest to you, enabling you to search for programming that interests you and recommending programming to you based on your past viewing, or
assisting third parties with media, programming and content planning and purchasing efforts. We, or third parties working for or with us, may also
use this information to distribute relevant programming and advertising to you without disclosing personally identifiable information about you to
programmers or advertisers. Some of these programs or advertisements may invite your participation, which you can accept or decline by using
your program guide commands or by following any special instructions on your video screen. We or third parties (such as audience measurement
firms, market research firms and data companies) also sometimes combine anonymous and/or aggregate viewing and other information with
additional demographic information (such as census records, gender, marital status, age, income, education and occupation, for example) and may
use or share it with others for purposes such as audience analysis, programming, marketing, advertising and other purposes. We will not provide
third parties that are not involved with the provision of services to you with personally identifiable information about you unless we have received
your consent first, except as required or permitted by law.
In addition to this privacy notice, we may provide additional notices to you regarding specific advertising or other initiatives. These notices will
describe the initiatives in greater detail and may, as appropriate, contain information you can use to choose to participate, or not participate, in
these initiatives.

II. USE OF YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION AND CPNI
We collect, maintain, and use personally identifiable information and CPNI as permitted by the Cable Act and the Telecommunications Act and
other applicable laws. We use this information primarily to conduct business activities related to providing you with our cable service and other
services, and to help us detect theft of service. Generally speaking, we use personally identifiable information in connection with: (i) billing, invoicing
and credit verification; (ii) administration; (iii) surveys; (iv) collection of fees and charges; (v) marketing; (vi) service delivery and customization; (vii)
maintenance and operations; (viii) technical support; (ix) hardware and software upgrades; and (x) fraud prevention.
More specifically, we also use personally identifiable information to: (i) install, configure, operate, provide, support, and maintain our cable service and
other services; (ii) investigate your credit history by obtaining a credit report or other similar information and/or making inquires of account histories; (iii)
confirm you are receiving the level(s) of service requested and are properly billed; (iv) identify you when changes are made to your account or services;
(v) make you aware of new products, programming or services that may be of interest to you; (vi) understand the use of, and identify improvements
to, our services; (vii) detect unauthorized reception, use, or abuse of our services; (viii) determine whether there are violations of any applicable policies
and terms of service; (ix) manage the network supporting our services; (x) configure cable service and other service-related devices; (xi) authenticate
(or allow others to authenticate) your right to access certain services, including Online Content; and (xii) comply with law.
The Telecommunications Act further permits WOW! to use, disclose, and permit access to CPNI obtained from our customers, either directly or
indirectly, to: (i) initiate, render, bill, and collect for telecommunications services; (ii) protect our rights and property, and protect our users of these
services and other carriers from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of, or subscription to, these services; (iii) provide any inbound telemarketing,
referral, or administrative services to you for the duration of the call, if you initiated the call and you approve of the use of this information to provide
these services; and (iv) provide call location information concerning the user of a commercial mobile phone service. We are also permitted to use,
disclose or permit access to CPNI: (i) for the purpose of providing or marketing service offerings among the categories of service to which you
already subscribe; (ii) in our provision of inside wiring, installation, maintenance and repair services; and (iii) to market certain services (formerly
known as adjunct to basic services) such as speed dialing, computer-provided directory assistance, call monitoring, call tracing, call blocking, call
return, repeat dialing, call tracking, call waiting, caller I.D., call forwarding and certain centrex features.
With respect to phone services, except as provided above, unless we obtain your approval in accordance with our policies described below under
“Giving or withholding your approval for WOW! to use CPNI to market additional products and services to you” WOW! may not use CPNI to market
products and services to you other than the phone services.
WOW! transmits, and may collect and store for a period of time, personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information about you when
you use our high-speed Internet and phone services to: (i) send and receive email, video mail, and instant messages; (ii) transfer and share files;
(iii) make files accessible; (iv) visit websites; (v) place or receive calls; (vi) leave and receive voicemail messages; (vii) establish custom settings or
preferences; (viii) communicate with us for support; or (ix) otherwise use the services and their features.
Our transmission, collection, and storage of this information is necessary to render the services. In certain situations, third-party service providers
may transmit, collect, and store this information on our behalf to provide features of our services. These third parties are not permitted to use your
personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these features.
We or our suppliers may also combine personally identifiable information, which we collect as described in this notice as part of our regular
business records, with personally identifiable information obtained from third parties for the purpose of creating an enhanced database or business
records. We may use this database and these business records in marketing and other activities related to our cable service and other services.
We also maintain records of research concerning subscriber satisfaction and viewing habits, which are obtained from subscriber interviews and
questionnaires.
We may investigate your credit history by obtaining a credit report or other similar information and/or making inquires of account histories.
Generally, we will do this by providing your information (such as your social security number) to credit reporting agencies. When we obtain a credit
report or other similar information, we maintain this information in your account file and may disclose this information to third parties for reasonable
business purposes consistent with this Notice.
III. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION AND CPNI
The Cable Act provisions relating to disclosure of personally identifiable information
WOW! considers the personally identifiable information contained in our business records to be confidential. The Cable Act authorizes WOW! as a
cable operator to disclose personally identifiable information concerning any subscriber for the following purposes if the disclosure is: (i) necessary
to render, or conduct a legitimate business activity related to, the cable service or other services provided to the subscriber; (ii) required by law or
legal process (described below under “Disclosure of personally identifiable information and CPNI when required by law”); or (iii) of the names and
addresses of subscribers for “mailing list” or other purposes (subject to each subscriber’s right to prohibit or limit this disclosure and the CPNI Policy
described below under “WOW!’s ‘do not call’ and ‘do not mail’ lists”).
The Cable Act prohibits us from disclosing personally identifiable information concerning any subscriber for any purposes other than those listed
above without the subscriber’s prior written or electronic consent.
We may disclose personally identifiable information as provided for in the Cable Act when it is necessary to render, or conduct a legitimate
business activity related to, the cable service or other services we provide to you. These kinds of disclosures typically involve billing and collections,
administration, surveys, marketing, service delivery and customization, maintenance and operations, and fraud prevention, for example. We or our
suppliers may also collect, use, and disclose information about you in non-personally identifiable or aggregate formats, such as ratings surveys and
service usage and other statistical reports, which do not personally identify you, your particular viewing habits, or the nature of any transaction you
have made over the cable system. This anonymous information may be used by us for any reason and shared with affiliates, partners and other
third parties, including advertisers, content providers, data companies, ratings agencies, audience measurement and market research firms. The
frequency of any disclosure of personally identifiable information varies in accordance with our business needs and activities.
The Cable Act authorizes WOW! as a cable operator to disclose limited personally identifiable information to others, such as charities, marketing
organizations, or other businesses, for cable or non-cable “mailing list” or other purposes. From time to time we may disclose your name and
address for these purposes. However, you have the right to prohibit or limit this kind of disclosure by contacting us by telephone: (i) Customers in
Illinois, Indiana, Michigan and Ohio at 1-866-496-9669; and (ii) Customers in Alabama, Florida, Georgia, Kansas, South Carolina and Tennessee at
1-855-496-9929, or by sending us a written request as described below under “How to contact WOW!” Any “mailing list” and related disclosures
that we may make are limited by the Cable Act to disclosures of subscriber names and addresses where the disclosures do not reveal, directly
or indirectly, (i) the extent of any viewing or other use by the subscriber of a cable service or other service provided by us; or (ii) the nature of any
transaction made by the subscriber over our cable system.

We may sometimes disclose personally identifiable information about you to our affiliates or to others who work for or with us, such as third party
vendors or service providers who provide us with equipment and/or services in connection with the services that we provide to you. We may
also disclose personally identifiable information about you to outside auditors, professional advisors, service providers and vendors, potential
business merger, acquisition, or sale partners, and regulators. We make these disclosures as provided for in the Cable Act. Typically, we make these
disclosures when the disclosure is necessary to render, or conduct a legitimate business activity related to, the cable service or other services we
provide to you. We may be required by law or legal process to disclose certain personally identifiable information about you to lawyers and parties
in connection with litigation and to law enforcement personnel. We may also disclose certain personally identifiable information about you to third
parties such as, for example, charities, marketing organizations, or other businesses, in connection with disclosures made for “mailing list” or other
purposes as described above under “Disclosure of your personally identifiable information and CPNI.”
If we (or our parent company) enter into a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, subscribers’ personally identifiable information
will, in most instances, be one of the items transferred as part of the transaction. If this notice will be changed as a result of a transaction like that,
you should refer below under “Changes to this notice.”
We may also use or disclose personally identifiable information about you without your consent to protect our customers, employees, or property,
in emergency situations, to enforce our rights under our terms of service and policies, in court or elsewhere, and as otherwise permitted by law.
Disclosure of personal information to others in connection with phone service
WOW! may disclose to others personally identifiable information in connection with features and services such as Caller ID, 911/E911, and directory
services as follows:
   • We may transmit your name and/or telephone number to be displayed on a Caller ID device unless you have elected to block such
       information. Please note that Caller ID blocking may not prevent the display of your name and/or telephone number when you dial
       certain business or emergency numbers, 911, 900 numbers, or toll free 800, 888, 877, or 866 numbers.
   • We may provide your name, address, and telephone number to public safety authorities and their vendors for inclusion in E911
       databases and records, inclusion in “reverse 911” systems, or to troubleshoot 911/E911 record errors.
   • We may publish and distribute, or cause to be published and distributed, telephone directories in print, on the Internet, and on disks.
       Those telephone directories may include subscriber names, addresses, and telephone numbers, without restriction to their use.
   • We may also make subscriber names, addresses, and telephone numbers available, or cause such subscriber information to be made
       available, through directory assistance operators.
   • We may provide subscribers’ names, addresses, and telephone numbers to unaffiliated directory publishers and directory assistance
       providers for their use in creating directories and offering directory assistance services.
   • Once our subscribers’ names, addresses, and telephone numbers appear in telephone directories or directory assistance, they may be
       sorted, packaged, repackaged and made available again in different formats by anyone.
We take reasonable precautions to ensure that non-published and unlisted numbers are not included in our telephone directories or directory
assistance services, but we cannot guarantee that errors will never occur. There is a fee for subscribers who choose to have non-published or
unlisted numbers.
Disclosure of personally identifiable information and CPNI when required by law
We make reasonable efforts to protect subscriber privacy as described in this notice. Nevertheless, we may be required by law to disclose personally
identifiable information or individually identifiable CPNI about a subscriber without his or her consent and without notice in order to comply with a
valid legal process such as a subpoena, court order, or search warrant.
For subscribers to our cable television service, the Cable Act requires WOW! as a cable operator to disclose personally identifiable information to a
third-party or governmental entity in response to a court order. If the court order is sought by a non-governmental entity, we are required to notify
the subscriber of the court order. If the court order is sought by a governmental entity, the Cable Act requires that the cable subscriber be afforded
the opportunity to appear and contest in a court proceeding relevant to the court order any claims made in support of the court order. At the
proceeding, the Cable Act requires the governmental entity to offer clear and convincing evidence that the subject of the information is reasonably
suspected of engaging in criminal activity and that the information sought would be material evidence in the case.
For subscribers to our high-speed Internet and phone services, the Cable Act requires WOW! to disclose personally identifiable information and
individually identifiable CPNI to a private third party in response to a court order, and we are required to notify the subscriber of the court order.
The Cable Act requires us to disclose personally identifiable information and individually identifiable CPNI about subscribers to high-speed Internet
and phone services to a government entity in response to a subpoena, court order, or search warrant, for example. We are often prohibited from
notifying the subscriber of any disclosure of personally identifiable information to a government entity by the terms of the subpoena, court order,
or search warrant.
WOW!’s protection of your personally identifiable information
We follow industry-standard practices to take such actions as are necessary to prevent unauthorized access to personally identifiable information
by a person other than the subscriber or us. However, we cannot guarantee that these practices will prevent every unauthorized attempt to access,
use, or disclose personally identifiable information.
Period that WOW! maintains personally identifiable information
WOW! maintains personally identifiable information about you in our regular business records while you are a subscriber to our cable service or
other services. We also maintain this information for a period of time after you are no longer a subscriber if the information is necessary for the
purposes for which it was collected or to satisfy legal requirements. These purposes typically include business, legal, or tax purposes. If these
purposes no longer apply, we will destroy the information according to our internal policies and procedures.
IV. ADDITIONAL INTERNET PRIVACY INFORMATION
We provide below in this Section additional information pertaining to our Internet Service and website (referred to in this Section as the “Service”).
Use of our website is further subject to the WOW! Website Visitor Agreement and the WOW! Website Privacy Statement, both of which are available
for review at our website.
Provision and transmission of information
We will not read your outgoing or incoming email, video mail, private chat, or instant messages, but we (or our third party providers) do store email
messages and video mail messages on computer systems for a period of time. We could be required to disclose these messages or be required
to store these messages and communications along with other personally identifiable information about you for an extended period to comply
with law or to protect our Service as described in this WOW! Customer Privacy Notice. We also monitor the performance of our Service and your

service connection in order to manage, maintain, and improve the Service and your connection to it. We (or our third party providers) use tools
to help prevent and block “spam” emails, viruses, spyware, and other harmful or unwanted communications and programs on the Service. These
tools may automatically scan your emails, video mails, instant messages, file attachments, and other files and communications in order to help us
protect you and the Service against these harmful or unwanted communications and programs. However, these tools do not collect or disclose
personally identifiable information about you. You should also be aware that any personally identifiable information you provide in forums, chat
areas, instant message services, or bulletin boards may be read, collected, and used by others who access those services. We are not responsible
for any personally identifiable information you choose to submit in forums, chat areas, instant message services, bulletin boards, or any other
publicly accessible service or website.
Third party advertisers and WOW! advertisements
We may use or partner with a third party advertising company (or companies) who may use cookies, web beacons, or other technologies to
deliver or facilitate delivery of advertisements about goods and services tailored to your location and/or interests you have shown by browsing
on WOW! and other websites you have visited. It also helps determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before in order to avoid
sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, the advertising company collects non-personally identifiable information such as your browser
type, your operating system, web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other click stream data. See further discussion
of “Cookies” below. When you visit the WOW! website, providers, such as Google, may use cookies or web beacons to note which product and
service descriptions your browser visited. When you are presented with WOW! advertisements on other websites, we or these providers may
use that information to select advertisements related to your interests. For example, a third party vendor such as Google may display a WOW!
advertisement to you when you visit another website not affiliated with WOW!. This is intended to provide you with an additional opportunity to look
at WOW! offerings that may be of interest to you. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these providers is subject to their
own privacy policies, not WOW!’s privacy policy for this website. If you do not want the benefits of the cookies used by these providers, you may
opt-out of them by visiting http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp or by visiting their opt-out pages. The advertising network
providers and/or audience segmenting technology providers that may collect information about your use of our website, and links to their opt-out
pages, are available using this hyperlink: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/.
In some service areas, WOW! may also use geographic location information to allow WOW! and its advertisers to display online relevant
advertisements to you. This type of location-based advertising uses the zip code, including the last four digits, location of your cable modem to
identify your service area. Online ads are then displayed to you with content tailored to your local service area. You will not receive more advertising
than you otherwise would. We will not as part of this service share with others any information that identifies you personally, and this service does
not use your Internet browsing history. Visit www.wowway.com/support/internet for more information about this location-based advertising. If we
use location–based advertising in your service area, you can always choose to opt-out of the service. To opt-out of this service, visit wowway.net
and login to manage your preferences.
Please review our WOW! Website Privacy Statement and WOW! Website Visitor Agreement for additional information about the types of information
that we collect from you when you visit our website and how we use that information.
Software and configuration
You have the choice to provide any information to a support representative, and you have the ability to confirm your decision before sending any
information to our systems. The information collected by our support team is limited to any emails you send or discussions you have during a
live support session. This information is available only to authorized personnel for maintaining and supporting the use of the Service. WOW! also
provides customer contact and support pages on the Service that you can use to communicate with WOW! about technical support.
WOW! uses the information provided by you on these pages to support your use of the Service WOW! may also offer or provide software directly or
though third parties for your use in connection with the Service. For example, we may provide software you can use for security, search, parental
controls, digital photographs, gaming, instant messaging, and video emails.
These programs may be subject to their own terms of service and other policies. You should carefully read their terms and policies to understand
how they may use personally identifiable information about you.
In certain cases, at your request or with or without prior notice to you, WOW! may configure your Service or Service-related equipment to resolve a
technical support issue or otherwise render or deliver the Service. WOW! may perform these configurations remotely over the cable network and/
or the Internet.
Preferences
We store information that you provide to personalize your settings on the Service so that you don’t have to change these settings each time you
use the Service. We do not share your preferences with third parties except for service providers or other third parties who may provide certain
components of the Service.
Cookies
Cookies are small files stored on a computer’s hard drive to simplify and improve a user’s Web experience. A website may store information in a
cookie about your computer configuration so that it can more efficiently provide information to you the next time you visit the site. Or, your browser
program might save a cookie with your username and password so that a website’s server will automatically recognize you the next time you
access the site.
WOW! uses cookies, among other things, to remember your geo location/market and your username and password, if you choose to store them,
from the home page of the Service at www.wowway.com, as well as to remember some of your personalization preferences and Service plan
features. WOW! does not store your name or other personal information in cookies.
Some of our business relationships are with vendors who may use cookies. For example, search engines or network advertising providers, or in
connection with the vendor’s own advertisers and other business partners. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. For more
information about how these vendors and their business partners use cookies, and how you may be able to “opt-out” of those cookies, read the
privacy policy that applies to each vendor’s website. This policy covers the use of cookies by WOW! on the www.wowway.com website only; it does
not cover the use of cookies by any other party or website unless stated otherwise.
Most Web browsers allow you to delete cookies and can be set to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the
opportunity to refuse that cookie. You may read more about enabling, disabling, and deleting cookies at www.wowway.com at any time by searching
for “cookie” and clicking on the link for the topic you wish to read. For complete information regarding our use of cookies, and for more information
about how you can manage cookies, please review our WOW! Website Privacy Statement and WOW! Website Visitor Agreement.

Log files and website and email management
Like many websites, WOW!’s website servers use log files. These logs record aggregate (non-personally identifiable) information about site usage
such as Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser types, Internet service providers, referring/exit pages, pages accessed, platform types, date/time
stamps, times of use, and numbers of clicks, for example. This information is necessary to analyze trends, administer the Service’s website, balance
web traffic, evaluate users’ electronic browsing in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP
addresses to personally identifiable information except as may be required to comply with law and as described in this WOW! Customer Privacy
Notice.
We use a software technology called Web Bugs (also known as Web Beacons/clear gifs) with the log files for the Service’s website www.wowway.
com. These Web Bugs are usually 1 by 1 pixel invisible images on our website’s pages. When a user visits one of these Web pages, the user’s browser
contacts our Web servers and creates an entry in the log for the website www.wowway.com. These entries do not use personally identifiable
information and they provide us with more accurate website visit and session information in the log files. We also use clear gifs on the Service’s
website to help format graphic elements.
We (or our third party providers) also use clear gifs in some of the emails that we send to you as described in this Policy. These clear gifs (also known
as email sensors) are small invisible images included in HTML-based emails. These clear gifs have two functions. First, they determine whether
an email recipient has opened a particular email. This helps us improve the wording of subject lines and content as well as determine readership
levels. Second, they determine whether an email recipient is capable of receiving an HTML-based email. This helps us customize email content
and improve your overall customer experience. WOW! owns the information collected by using email sensors, and our third party providers are
obligated to keep this information confidential and not share this information with anyone else or use it for any other purpose. If you do not want
to receive emails that use email sensors, you can set up your email program so that it does not accept HTML-based email, and instead uses only
plain text format for email.
Links
The Service’s website contains links to other sites. Some of these other sites may be co-branded with WOW! and may look like Service features, but
WOW! is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our website and to read the
privacy policies of every website that collects personally identifiable information about you, whether the site is co-branded with WOW! or not. WOW! is
not responsible for a third party website, or for the use, storage or disclosure of information that you provide to a third party. WOW! is not responsible
for webcasting or any other form of transmission received from any third party or linked site nor is WOW! responsible if the third party or linked site
is not working appropriately. WOW!’s provision of links or other access to a third party site does not imply endorsement by WOW! of the site or its
contents, or affiliation with its operators. By using our services, you assume all responsibility related to the security, privacy, and confidentiality risks
inherent in sending any content or information over the Internet, or providing personal information to a third party site. By its very nature, a website and
the Internet cannot be absolutely protected against intentional or malicious intrusion attempts. WOW! does not control the third party sites and the
Internet over which you may choose to send confidential personal information or other content and, therefore, WOW! does not warrant any safeguard
against any interceptions or compromises to your information, or how your information may be used by the third party site. When posting any content
or information on an Internet site, you should think carefully about your own privacy in disclosing detailed or private information about yourself and
your family.
URL Directs
If you type a Uniform Resource Locator (URL) which contains a nonexistent or unassigned domain name, or enter a search term into your browser
address bar, WOW! may present you with a WOW! web search page containing suggested links based upon the query you entered in lieu of your
receiving an NXDOMAIN, similar error message or browser assigned query. WOW!’s provision of the web search page may impact applications that
rely on an NXDOMAIN or similar error message and may override similar browser-based search results pages. If you would prefer not to receive
these pages from WOW!, you should follow the opt-out instructions that are available by clicking on the “About” or “Opt Out” link on the page.
Special note about children
The Service is not directed to children under the age of 13, and WOW! does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone
under the age of 18 on the Service unless expressly specified on the appropriate pages of the Service website. However, some pages of the Service
website may be of interest to children. On those pages, WOW! or its service providers will provide a special notice or other information describing
any additional privacy protections that may apply. Children should always get permission from a parent or legal guardian before sending any
information about themselves (such as their names, email addresses, and telephone numbers) over the Internet, to us or to anyone else.
Additional Website Terms and Privacy
WOW!‘s website is available to both WOW! customers and others. Use of the website is subject to the WOW! Website Visitor Agreement and
the WOW! Website Privacy Statement, both of which are available for review at our website. By accessing and using the WOW! website, you
acknowledge your review of and consent to the WOW! Website Visitor Agreement and the WOW! Website Privacy Statement.
V. CUSTOMER ACCESS AND CHOICE REGARDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION AND CPNI
You may examine and correct, if necessary, the personally identifiable information regarding you that is collected and maintained by WOW! in our
regular business records. In most cases, the personally identifiable information contained in these records consists solely of billing and account
information. We will correct our records if you make a reasonable showing that any of the personally identifiable information we have collected
about you is inaccurate.
If you have Internet access, you can view and change certain information yourself as follows: (i) For accounts you have established at the WOW!
website, use the My Account (or similar) feature at www.wowway.com; or (ii) For high-speed Internet accounts, use the My Account (or similar)
feature at www.wowway.com.
You may also examine the records containing your personally identifiable information at your local WOW! office upon reasonable prior notice to us
and during our regular business hours. If you wish to examine these records, please contact us by mail or telephone: (i) Customers in Illinois, Indiana,
Michigan and Ohio at 1-866-496-9669, and (ii) Customers in Alabama, Florida, Georgia, Kansas, South Carolina and Tennessee at 1-855-496-9929,
giving us a reasonable period of time to locate and, if necessary, prepare the information for review, and to arrange an appointment. You will only
be permitted to examine records that contain personally identifiable information about your account and no other account.
If you make an affirmative, written request for a copy of your CPNI, we will disclose the relevant information we have to you, or to any person
designated by you, if we can properly authenticate your identity. However, subscribers to our phone services should be aware that we generally
do not provide them with records of any inbound or outbound calls or other records that we don’t furnish in the ordinary course of business (for
example, as part of a bill) or which are available only from our archives, without valid legal process such as a court order. In addition, we cannot
correct any errors in customer names, addresses, or telephone numbers appearing in, or omitted from, our or our vendors’ directory lists until the

next available publication of those directory lists. Further, we may have no control over information appearing in the directory lists or directory
assistance services of directory publishers or directory assistance providers which are not owned by us or our subsidiaries.
WOW! must properly authenticate your identity prior to disclosing CPNI based on customer-initiated telephone contact, online account access, or
an in-store visit. We will only disclose call detail information over the telephone, based on customer-initiated telephone contact, if you can provide
us with all of the call detail information necessary to address a customer service issue (i.e., the telephone number called, when it was called, and, if
applicable, the amount charged for the call). Even under these circumstances, however, we will not disclose to you any call detail information about
your account other than the call detail information that you provide to us. If you require further call detail information, we will mail it to your address
of record or you can check the records online (in accordance with our online access and authentication procedures).
We must also authenticate your identity prior to allowing you online access to CPNI related to your account. You can access your account information
by following all of the registration and authentication procedures found on our website at www.wowway.com. Once authenticated, you may only
obtain online access to CPNI related to your account through a password. We will also disclose CPNI to you if you, at one of our retail locations, first
present to us or our agent a valid photo ID matching your account information.
If you are a business customer, some of these authentication regimes may not apply to you, depending on your specific agreement with WOW!. You
should consult your agreement with WOW! to determine how we have agreed to protect your CPNI. In all events, WOW! reserves the right to charge
you for the cost of retrieving and photocopying any documents that you request.
Giving or withholding your approval for WOW! to use CPNI to market additional products and services to you
WOW! provides IP-enabled or “VoIP” phone service in all of its operating regions. In addition, WOW!, through its operating affiliates, provides both
VoIP and traditional circuit switched phone service (“Traditional Phone”). In an Order released by the Federal Communications Commission in April
2007, the Commission modified its rules regarding CPNI and also determined that its rules (as modified) regarding CPNI apply to VoIP services
effective December 8, 2007. If you are a customer of our Traditional Phone services or (effective December 8, 2007) our VoIP phone services, you
have the right, and WOW! has a duty, under the Telecommunications Act, to protect the confidentiality of CPNI.
In addition to WOW! Phone, WOW! offers (either directly or through its agents and affiliates that provide communications related services) other
communications-related services, such as WOW! Internet and cable television services. From time to time we would like to use the CPNI information
we have on file to provide you with information about our communications-related products and services or special promotions. Our use of CPNI
may also enhance our ability to offer products and services tailored to your specific needs.
We would like your approval so that we may use this CPNI (or disclose it to our agents and affiliates that provide communications related services)
to let you know about communications related services other than those to which you currently subscribe that we believe may be of interest to
you. IF YOU APPROVE, YOU DO NOT HAVE TO TAKE ANY ACTION. HOWEVER, YOU DO HAVE THE RIGHT TO RESTRICT OUR USE OF YOUR CPNI.
You may deny or withdraw our right to use your CPNI at any time by calling the number listed below. If we do not hear from you within 30 days of
this notification, we will assume that you approve our use of CPNI for the purpose of providing you with information about other communications-
related services.
WOW! PHONE SERVICE – CALL US: (i) Customers in Illinois, Indiana, Michigan and Ohio at 1-866-496-9669 and (ii) Customers in Alabama, Florida,
Georgia, Kansas, South Carolina and Tennessee at 1-855-496-9929.
We may also occasionally ask you during a telephone call with one of our representatives for your oral consent to WOW!’s use of your CPNI for the
purpose of providing you with an offer for non-communications related products and services. If you provide your oral consent for WOW! to do so,
WOW! may use your CPNI only for the duration of that telephone call in order to offer you additional services.
If you deny or restrict your approval for us to use your CPNI, you will suffer no effect, now or in the future, on how we provide any services to which
you subscribe. Any denial or restriction of your approval remains valid until your services are discontinued or you affirmatively revoke or limit such
approval or denial. You may disregard this notice if you previously contacted us in response to a CPNI notification and denied use of your CPNI for
the purposes described above.
WOW!’s “do not call” and “do not mail” lists
You may contact WOW! as follows: (i) Customers in Illinois, Indiana, Michigan and Ohio at 1-866-496-9669 and (ii) Customers in Alabama, Florida,
Georgia, Kansas, South Carolina and Tennessee at 1-855-496-9929, to ask us to put your name on our “do not call” and “do not mail” lists so that
you do not receive marketing or promotional telephone calls or postal mail from us or made at our request. You also have the right to prohibit or
limit disclosure of your personally identifiable information for “mailing list” or other purposes as described above in this notice by contacting us at
the numbers above.
WOW!’s use of your account information for marketing and promotional activities is also subject to your right to limit or restrict us from making
those offers as described above in “Giving or withholding your approval for WOW! to use CPNI to market additional products and services to you”
in this notice.
If you prefer to contact WOW! in writing instead of by telephone, you may send a written request to the address listed below under “How to contact
WOW!.” Be sure to include your name and address, your WOW! account number, and a daytime telephone number where you can be reached in
the event we have any questions about your request. The written request should be signed by the person who is identified in our billing records as
the subscriber. If you have a joint account, a request by one party will apply to the entire account. If you have multiple accounts, your notice must
separately identify each account covered by the request.
Online and Remote Access to Services
As part of its video service, WOW! may provide for online or remote access to certain programming and other content, which may be accessed by
you by use of a computer, or a mobile access or similar device (the “Online Content”). You (and members of your household) are allowed access to
the Online Content by use of a WOW! password (or other similar credentials). You should take special care to maintain the confidentiality of your
password and other credentials, as password sharing with persons outside of your immediate household (that would allow those persons access
to the Online Content) is prohibited. The availability of such Online Content varies depending upon your service location and the level of service to
which you subscribe, and is subject to change.
By accessing the Online Content, you agree and understand that: (i) your access to Online Content is subject to the WOW! terms of service and
this privacy policy (the “Terms”), which are subject to change, as well as additional terms and conditions imposed by the Online Content provider;
(ii) airtime or data charges may apply and are your responsibility, so please check with your carrier; (iii) you are responsible for keeping your
password and other credentials confidential, as password sharing with persons outside your household is prohibited; (iv) WOW! may use its system
and equipment to collect, use and store information regarding your use of the service, and may disclose anonymous usage information to Online
Content providers and others; and (v) WOW! may also provide information about you to Online Content providers or their vendors so that they

can: (a) verify that you are an authorized WOW! subscriber who has authority to access the Online Content, and (b) identify certain characteristics
about you, such as your service location. For example, we may provide to content providers information such as your WOW! subscription status,
globally unique identifier, zip code and other identification information. The content providers may use and store the information for purposes of
authenticating your access rights and providing Online Content to you, including, for example, professional sports programming that is subject
to league blackout rules based on a viewer’s zip code. The content providers may also share anonymous information regarding you that WOW!
provides to them for various other commercial purposes such as selling advertising and generating ratings information for the programming.
In addition, to access some Online Content, you may be re-directed to a website that is not controlled by or affiliated with WOW! (a “third party site”),
and is subject to its own terms and conditions and policies. WOW! has no responsibility for the Online Content or any other aspect of the third party
site, or for the use, storage or disclosure of information that you provide to a third party. WOW! is not responsible for webcasting or any other form
of transmission received from any third party or linked site nor is WOW! responsible if the third party or linked site is not working appropriately.
WOW!’s provision of links or other access to a third party site does not imply endorsement by WOW! of the site or its contents, or affiliation with its
operators. You are responsible for viewing and abiding by the privacy statements and terms of use posted at the third party sites.
When you access Online Content provided by Internet-based companies not affiliated with WOW!, such as Netflix®, Amazon Instant Video (C), Hulu
Plus® and You Tube® (“Internet Content Providers”), by use of your WOW!-provided set-top box or other device, you further understand, agree and
acknowledge that: (i) the Online Content is not provided by WOW! and WOW! has no responsibility for it; and (ii) you are subject to the terms of use,
pricing, privacy policies and other rules established solely by such Internet Content Providers. You should review those terms and policies prior to
accessing the Online Content or any third party website by use of the WOW! Services or equipment; and (iii) WOW! is not responsible for any account
(or other interaction or relationship) that you may establish with such Internet Content Providers; and (iv) when you access the Online Content, you
are leaving the WOW! controlled experience and therefore you will generally not receive WOW! emergency alert system (EAS) messaging; provided,
however, you agree that we may in our discretion terminate your session with an Internet Content Provider (and interrupt your access to the Online
Content) in order to transmit EAS messages.
Email and other communications from WOW!
We may send a welcome email and sometimes other information to new subscribers to our cable service and other services (including each new
secondary account holder, where applicable). We may also send service-related announcements and notices to our subscribers from time to time.
For example, we may send you an email announcement about a pricing change, a change in operating policies, a service appointment, or new
features of one or more of the cable service or other services you receive from us. You may not opt-out of these service-related communications.
If you fail to check your primary WOW! email address for service-related announcements, you may miss important information about our services,
including legal notices, for example.
We reserve the right to send you promotional or commercial email as permitted by applicable law. You understand, agree and consent that
commercial email messages may be sent to your wireless or mobile device and there may be a charge from your wireless or mobile device provider.
You can manage the promotional or commercial emails WOW! may send to you by following the instructions contained in the emails. If you no longer
wish to receive these emails you may opt-out of receiving them by clicking the link in the emails for unsubscribe. We also ask that you provide us
with a contact telephone number (which may be your home telephone, your cell phone, or another number that you provide to us). You understand
and agree that the contact phone number that you provide to us will be used by us to contact you with promotional and/or informational messages
about your services (for example, we may call or email you about a new product or promotion or if there will be a change or interruption in your
services, there is a price or feature change for your service, or if we have a question about or want to provide you with information concerning your
services, billing statement or a past due invoice), and may include autodialed, pre-recorded and/or artificial voice messages. You understand and
agree that certain calls and emails (such as calls to a cell phone or an email to a wireless device) may result in data or airtime charges from your
carrier, which are your responsibility. Please be sure to tell us immediately if your contact telephone number or email address changes. You are not
required to consent to our calling you with promotional messages in order to use our services.
You understand and agree that when we communicate with you by phone, the call may be recorded for quality assurance purposes.
What to do if you think your privacy rights have been violated
If you believe that you have been aggrieved by any act of ours in violation of the Cable Act, we encourage you to contact us directly as described
below in “How to contact WOW!” in order to resolve your question or concern. You may also enforce the limitations imposed on us by the Cable Act
as applicable with respect to your personally identifiable information through a civil lawsuit seeking damages, attorney’s fees, and litigation costs.
Other rights and remedies may be available to you under federal or other applicable laws as well.
Changes to this Notice
As required by the Cable Act, we will provide you with a copy of this customer privacy notice at the time we enter into an agreement to provide
any cable service or other service to you, and annually afterwards, or as otherwise permitted by law. You can view the most current version of this
notice by going to www.wowway.com and selecting the “privacy” link at the bottom of the page.
We may modify this notice at any time. We will notify you of any material changes through written, electronic, or other means and as otherwise
permitted by law. If you find the changes to this notice unacceptable, you have the right to cancel your service. If you continue to use the service
following notice of the changes, we will consider that to be your acceptance of and consent to the changes in the revised privacy notice. This
includes your consent for any personally identifiable information that we may collect and use starting on the effective date of the revised notice,
as well as for any personally identifiable information that we have collected prior to the effective date of the revised notice. However, we will only
consider your continued use of the service to be your acceptance of and consent to changes in the revised privacy notice for changes made after
the initial effective date of this revised notice.
How to contact WOW!
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding this privacy notice, or wish to contact us about your personal information, please reach us as
follows:
Phone: (i) Customers in Illinois, Indiana, Michigan and Ohio at 1-866-496-9669 and (ii) Customers in Alabama, Florida, Georgia, Kansas, South
Carolina and Tennessee at 1-855-496-9929.
Website: www.wowway.com
Mail: (i) Customers in Illinois, Indiana, Michigan and Ohio, WOW!, P.O. Box 63000, Colorado Springs, CO 80962, and (ii) Customers in Alabama, Florida,
Georgia, Kansas, South Carolina and Tennessee, WOW!, 1241 O. G. Skinner Drive, West Point, GA 31833.
Revised and effective: October 24, 2016
                                                                                                                                              RES2017PRI
